{
    "word parameters": {
        "excluded": [
            "abuse",
            "abused",
            "abusing",
            "assault",
            "assaulted",
            "assaulting",
            "rape",
            "raped",
            "raping",
            "molest",
            "molested",
            "molesting",
            "suicide",
            "suicidal",
            "kill",
            "killer",
            "killing",
            "update",
            "edit",
            "UPDATE:",
            "edit:"
        ],
        "minimum length question": "20",
        "maximum length question": "500",
        "minimum length answer": "20",
        "maximum length answer": "400"
    },
    "before": {
        "mean length of answer": "85.24647887323944",
        "mean length of question": "222.68661971830986",
        "std question": "177.24999363470587",
        "std_answer": "75.45091554524538",
        "longest answer": "804",
        "longest question": "1219",
        "shortest answer": "31",
        "shortest question": "10",
        "number of items": "284"
    },
    "after": {
        "mean length of answer": "84.19047619047619",
        "mean length of question": "182.84656084656083",
        "std question": "110.4085378922073",
        "std_answer": "63.120575924687564",
        "longest answer": "393",
        "longest question": "498",
        "shortest answer": "31",
        "shortest question": "20",
        "number of items": "189"
    }
}